Kenjiro, Sir.
Thank you.
Hey!
Stay alert.
- Sir!
Sir.
- Sir.
Ah, it's you Kenjiro.
I thought it was the woman.
Excuse me, Oyabun. She's almost here.
Excuse me.
Does it have to go this far though?
It's not the first time
someone has tried to kill me.
To kill me.
With all due respect, Oyabun.
This time,
it's different.
We suspect it's the Shi no kage.
That's what the others call them…
No one knows who leads them,
who hires them.
They lay await in the dark,
and before you know it…
From your neck,
death whistles.
The last thing you'll see
is your blood painting the floor red.
What the hell, Kenji.
The fuck are you on about?
Shadows?
They're sending ninjas?
Forgive me.
Who's there?
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Oyabun.
The woman you requested.
Now you know what to do, right?
That's it.
Keep your back to me.
Take your clothes off!
I'm sorry, Dear.
I'll be home in two to three days.
But Mika wants Papa home tonight.
Please, Papa.
Mika, I promise you.
Get ready!
I'm going to fuck you now!
Huh?
What's that?
- I have to go.
- But...
What's wrong?
You, you.
Oyabun?
Oyabun!
- Hey!
- What the…
Shit. What the hell happened here?
You!
Who did this?
Answer me!
Stop!
Damn!
Kill this asshole.
Do you want to fight?
Bastard!
What the hell?
Let's go guys!
Tell everyone to stay alert!
The attacker may not be alone.
- Yes, Sir!
Hey, let's go.
Secure this area.
Keep looking!
A woman?
What's going on?
Now what?
Get the lights back on. Now!
- Yes, Sir!
Show yourself, damn it!
Hey.
Why you…
Come on then!
You asshole!
Shoot now!
Shi no kage.
Shadow.
You've killed Yoshinori.
Why? Why do you keep killing?
- I'm just a...
- We are hired
to eliminate the entire Onori clan.
Yoshinori
is only head of clan.
Kenjiro Kayama.
With the death of Yoshinori,
you're next
in line.
The entire clan
has been annihilated.
I won't last.
No one
chooses their fate.
Damn it.
13.
13!
Breathe.
Breathe. Slowly.
We're done here.
Take your gear.
What's next?
Umbra?
Ma'am?
I'm sorry.
Instructor Umbra.
I'm questioning your competence
over future missions.
Did I fail?
Yes.
But I neutralized
the main target and other...
You were compromised.
Yoshinori was not a volatile target.
It will only get harder.
And look what happened.
You were distracted.
That's why you failed.
I wasn't briefed on the woman.
Our mission is never easy.
But never complex.
We're neutralizers.
Not rescuers nor negotiators.
We strictly kill.
If you can't understand that.
Why are you even here?
We've invested time and effort
to forge you as the best.
Remember that, 13.
I'm not just a number.
I have a name.
My name is…
That's enough.
Take this.
You think I'm being harsh.
It's nothing compared to
what I experienced.
Your instructor then.
Instructor Burai.
Master.
Master Burai.
Now rest.
A change of plan.
One cargo to Jakarta, Indonesia.
Me and the other one
are catching the next flight.
Yes, that's all.
Take your gear.
Medic will check on you.
Listen, 13.
Fulfilling the mission
is our purpose in life.
Life?
What life?
LEADER FATHER, DEVOTED SON
- Please, state your code.
- 13.
Please state the purpose of communication.
Seeking instructions from Umbra.
Hello?
Are you taking
your prescriptions, Agent 13?
Yes.
We hope all is cleared
until your next briefing.
Your commitment and dedication
are always appreciated.
PLEASE PAY YOUR WELFARE
AND WATER BILLS ON TIME
Let's go, Mom.
Just a bit more.
A bit more.
Please forgive your mom.
Now, you won't have anything
to worry about.
But I don't want you seeing him.
You promised you won't work
with him anymore.
I promise I won't.
I won't work with him anymore.
And I promise, from now on
we won't be poor.
You're gonna be a big brother soon, Monji.
Let's go, Mom.
Come on, Mom.
Come on.
Asti.
Asti!
What the fuck are you doing here, Haga?
You know why I'm here.
Mind your own business.
It's my business with Ariel.
Fuck off!
Fuck you!
Get lost, all of you!
Fuck!
That's my mother!
You piece of shit!
Monji!
Get inside, you little fuck.
Monji.
Hey.
- Get lost!
- Monji,
now you're all alone.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Let me know if you need anything, okay?
Go inside.
- Please, state your code.
- 13.
Seeking instructions from Umbra.
Instructor Umbra.
Agent 13,
you are instructed to wait
until further notice.
Till when?
It's been two weeks.
Are you taking your prescription?
Yes, I've been fucking taking it!
I'm sorry.
It's just that I haven't heard anything…
from…
We hope all is cleared
until your next briefing.
Your commitment and dedication
are always appreciated.
Aren't you gonna eat that?
What?
If you're not gonna eat it, I want it.
Are you okay?
This?
It's nothing.
Hang in there, okay?
What do you mean?
I saw
your mom
the other day…
It can't be helped.
She had it coming.
She was an addict,
and so she OD-ed.
I saw those men
at your place that night.
Just her usual “customers”.
Her customers beat you up?
Won't you shut up?
It's just fucking meatballs!
Fucking lousy mom.
Had to look after her since I was a kid.
Should've been the other way around.
After all that she still dies.
Fuck her.
And still you loved her.
She was a burden.
And now I'm free.
So the knife you're carrying
isn't for revenge?
They say she OD-ed.
No!
They killed her.
"They"?
She worked for people who…
I tried to protect her.
But Haga…
He beats me up.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I still want you around, Mom.
Monji.
Let's go see your mom.
I'm scared.
It's all right.
It's spooky.
Hey, trust me. These guys
can't do anything now.
What was your mom's name, again?
Asti?
Mirasti.
MIRASTI, DAUGHTER OF SOEDARWO
A beautiful name.
Thank you.
Go on.
You said you wanted to talk to her.
I'll show you how.
Say anything you want.
Your mom will always be listening.
Mom…
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
I still want to be with you, Mom.
Still want to cook for you.
And rub your back.
I still want you around, Mom.
Thank you, Sis.
Actually, what's your name?
Let's meet again tomorrow,
and I'll tell you.
Mommy!
THANK YOU, SIS
Monji?
Hello, Boss?
You there yet?
Yeah, I'm at Asti's.
Start looking.
What am I looking for?
Fuckhead.
Find anything that can be evidence.
- All right.
- Jeki,
if anything's traced back to me…
Okay, got it.
Everyone goes down.
Hello? Boss Haga?
Hello?
Goddamnit.
Fuck you, man.
Those at the top forget
The ones at the bottom
Jackpot!
Damn, good shit.
Real good.
Where is he?
Who?
Monji!
Where is he?
Fuck!
Where is Monji?
I can't breathe.
You said "Haga".
That's my boss!
He told me to come here.
- Take me to him.
- To who?
To Haga?
Are you out of your mind? No way!
- Move it!
- Shit!
You got a dead wish, going after Haga.
Do you know who he runs with?
Who?
Those guys.
Like father, like son.
LEADER FATHER, DEVOTED SON
Both have loose screws in their head.
Just pray you don't get involved
with them.
What's that got to do with Haga?
Haga's the pimp.
And Prasetyo's the cop
and his goons.
Then there's Ariel.
The vicious one.
They grew up together.
Now, they deep into fucked up shit.
Anyone disappears for good
would have something to do with them.
And the police?
Police?
This is Jakarta, Missy.
Where are we going?
Haga
and his twin, Soriah.
They run Moonrose.
- Let's go.
- Hold up.
What's your plan?
I've told you,
I'm looking for Monji.
He mentioned Haga's name.
Who the fuck are you to Monji?
- He's a friend! Now get the door!
- Okay.
Monji's here. He has to be here!
Shush! We don't know that yet.
Don't cause any troubles.
That's Soriah.
Ariel agreed.
In two days, you bring cold cash,
we hand you the stuff.
Brother' Kabil.
Our next meeting here…
will make us partners.
Shit, Ariel is so full of himself.
Why am I talking to his whore curator?
What do you call a woman
who pimps other women out?
She does that, doesn't she?
Hang on.
What are you gonna say?
I'm gonna ask where Monji is.
You're gonna ask where Monji is?
That's not how you do it.
Ariel's smart.
He won't carelessly
meet some petty thug.
It's not a secret
how you're still in the game.
With that habit
of stabbing people in the back.
Look at me.
The difference between you and me…
I stab you
while you're looking.
That mouth
is gonna get you killed
one day.
Let's go.
Act dumb, trust me.
I brought a gift for you guys.
For Haga.
Go on in.
Why is this rookie whore so built?
Name?
What's your name?
- Are you deaf?
- Sari.
Her name is Sari.
Sorry, she is a bit shy.
Sari?
Don't look like one.
Soriah, I'm sorry.
But where's the boss?
What's up?
About Monji.
It better be important.
You stay here.
Lock the door.
- No.
- Shush.
Everything will be all right.
Is it done?
Yeah, Boss.
I've cleaned up the place.
So if I send someone there,
they won't find anything
that might be traced back to me, right?
Absolutely not.
What happened to your face?
- Get the fuck off me!
- Shut it!
- You used my stuff?
- No, Boss.
I swear.
Jeki.
Your face,
your ass,
everything belongs to me.
The only difference between you
and her is…
she's still worth something.
Do you fucking understand?
Yes, Boss.
He brought a girl here,
said it's for you.
I met her at Monji's place.
Really?
- Bring the girl in.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Why are you alone...
Who the fuck are you, Kid?
I swear, Boss. I don't know who she is.
She suddenly...
Where's Monji?
This is Monji's.
So what?
Haga!
You killed Haga! You're dead, fuckers!
Jeki, bring her with you!
Let's get out of here!
Haga? I'm fucked.
Jeki!
Missy, here's the stairs.
You motherfucker!
Hey, slut!
Where are you?
Missy!
Let's go!
Hurry!
The cops are here!
Hurry up or I leave you behind!
Hurry up!
Help me, goddamnit!
Hey!
We can't leave her here!
She'll just slow me down!
- Let's go.
- Fuck this shit.
Stop!
Don't look at me like that!
You just dug my grave!
- You know, they never trusted you, right?
- Yeah!
But now they'll think I'm with you.
Damn it!
I saw Monji get taken away
by that policeman.
Fucking Monji.
Why do you care so much about him?
He's just…
Fuck!
Get out.
I can't help you anymore.
But I need your help to find Monji.
Not my problem!
Hey, you!
It's better if you don't go home tonight.
That's enough.
Please, stop!
You'll make him deaf.
Kusno.
Why?
Why did you drive the truckload
of meth to the harbor?
I swear it was not me, sir.
If you don't confess,
I can't help you.
Dad, when are you coming home?
I miss you.
I've been a good girl…
Are you sure you want to go on?
…at school, I…
Every morning, your daughter
goes to school at 5 am.
It would be a pity if her small body
collided with a car.
Or…
If an unknown van
took her.
No, sir.
Please! No! Take me instead.
No, sir. Please! No!
All right.
We don't want that now, do we?
None of us do.
Kusno, from the top.
Now tell me
how you drive the truckload
of meth to the harbor.
Hello, Riel.
A professional did this.
She's just a teenager,
but highly trained.
I've seen her before.
Yeah.
I heard she came around with Jeki.
Looking for Asti's son.
And Moonrose?
It will be all over the news.
- Call off your deal with Kabil!
- Yes, and...
- Ariel, I can't accept this.
- Pras!
I'm also upset about Haga.
So you know what to do.
- I'll start with Jeki.
- Yes.
Be careful.
I've got enough problems myself.
What did I tell you, Son?
Your mistakes snowballed
into something beyond your capacity.
Pop.
Don't worry, Pop.
I've spoken to Pras and the team.
Everything's gonna be okay.
So don't worry, I've set...
- Have they been put up?
- They're up, Sir.
Print the ones of myself too.
LEADER FATHER, DEVOTED SON
- Stand by, just in case.
- Pop!
If you'll excuse me, Sir.
I've told you
to take care of that woman you knocked up.
And I took care of it, didn't I?
I meant send her to a clinic
or anywhere else!
Not by killing her
when my campaign is up and running!
I'm only doing what you've done before.
Clean your mess.
Someone's looking for you.
Are you afraid?
You should be afraid.
I heard
adrenaline reduces the pain.
So…
Hey!
Troika.
Damn it.
Yes, Old Man.
Son of a bitch.
Emergency protocol initiated.
Are...
JEKI DJAMIL
I have five balloons
They come in different colors
Green, yellow, grey
Also pink and blue
My green one pops
Pop!
It breaks my heart
Make sure to take off your badges.
We're moving in.
I hold on tight
I have four left in my hands
Nana!
- Watch the door.
- Nana.
No, please, no.
I have five balloons
They come in different colors
- Green
Yellow, grey
Also pink and blue
Louder!
My green one pops
Nana!
Jeki, where is she?
Where's who?
Come on, Jeki!
Where's the kid who killed Haga?
If you don't tell me,
you'll be wiping off her brain matter!
Please. I don't know!
We split up after Moonrose!
Jeki…
You really think your grandma
is worth more than Haga?
Haga is all alone now.
He must be terrified in the dark!
- Do you get it?
- Please, I am all my grandma has.
There's movement outside, Boss.
Go check it.
Oh, no!
Don't you dare, Jeki!
Remember whose side you're on!
Where's Monji?
Monji?
So this whole mess is about one kid,
who because of you,
is going to die anyway.
Please, don't.
Ariel! I'm nearby, but she's getting away!
Don't lose sight of her. I'm ready.
Okay.
Ariel, let me have her.
Hey, Pras!
Take it easy, okay?
Okay?
Let me call Pop first.
You've killed someone dear to me.
So now,
I'm going to really enjoy...
Stop!
Pras!
Mommy?
Wake up, Mom.
I've seen my dad interrogate people here
since I was a kid and…
no one
ever got away.
You know what?
Just tonight,
you killed two of my best friends.
And for what?
For a son of a whore?
Why did you kill his mom?
You killed Haga and Prasetyo…
just because
I killed that whore?
What is she to you?
Nothing.
That kid should know
that his mom blackmailed me to marry her,
just because we fucked.
My pop's a gubernatorial candidate,
you fuck!
Gubernatorial candidate!
Do you realize what that means?
It means
one day,
I could also lead Jakarta.
You understand why you're fucked, right?
I understand now.
Behind that mask,
you're just a scared boy,
hiding behind daddy.
Soriah!
Hey.
Your head breaking
will be
music to my ears.
Don't kill her though.
Leave me something
for Haga.
Ariel!
Pop?
She's…
She's right.
You can't do anything right
when I'm not around.
Our men have died,
cops and your own friends.
She killed them, right?
You listen!
Whoever she is,
she can be useful for us.
What do you mean?
As long as that kid's around,
she'll do anything for us.
Understand?
Our deal with Kabil must go on.
Pop! Moonrose has been shut down.
- I have to cancel...
- Hey, look here!
You have to do the deal
with that Arab thug!
It's 2.5 million dollars, Ariel.
I know, Pop! I know!
I need it for my campaign!
Please, Pop.
Remember,
she can wipe out ten cops.
Kabil's men won't stand a chance.
Once the deal is done,
you can do whatever you want with her.
Take her to the harbor,
drown her with the kid.
Whatever you want, Son.
Prasetyo and Haga…
Once I'm governor,
there will be other Prasetyos
and Hagas for you.
There, there.
This is not how a governor's son
should look like.
I know
you're not an ordinary girl.
And I'm a fair man.
I don't need to know who you are.
You want the kid,
I want your services.
Monji.
Sis.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't forget my mom.
I still dream of her.
I understand.
I'm hungry.
Tomorrow,
we'll go eat meatballs again.
All the meatballs you want.
Okay?
All right.
See that guy?
Okay.
Here's the plan.
Once the deal is done
and we're safely back in the car,
you take out Kabil.
Right in the head.
I kill him,
and we'll all go down.
Well, you're strong.
So there's still a chance you'll survive.
Pop…
If anything happens to me,
choke the kid to death.
Jeez! It's hot in here.
- Hey!
- Come on.
Kabil!
Is that your daddy in the car?
That's so sweet.
The future governor looking after his son.
Do you bring the cash?
It's there.
Where's my stuff?
99% uncut.
Street value is twice your capital.
Well, I'm not the one
who wants to be governor.
She comes with the stuff?
A bonus.
Check the stuff.
Make sure he keeps his words.
Sir,
I think we have to take him
to the hospital.
Thank you.
Hey!
Check it!
Now, you let Monji go.
Soriah.
As soon as I get in the car,
you know what to do.
What about Monji?
Just do what I say!
Kabil!
Here, take her.
You want her, right?
Hey.
Monji.
Monji's gone.
- Monji!
- Shut him up!
Monji!
What happened to your face?
I don't want to do this.
What do you mean?
Monji's dead!
Missy!
Monji…
Monji's dead!
Monji!
Motherfucker!
Who's stabbing from the back now, huh?
Kill them all!
Stop standing around! Go!
Cover for me!
Wait.
Wait!
Dad!
Motherfuckers!
Pop!
Hey!
It's all your fault!
You should've trusted me!
Pop…
Look at you now!
Idiot!
Die, you fucks!
Die!
Kabil!
Wait, no, wait!
Shit!
The fuck are you wearing?
I won, motherfucker!
Where's the bitch?
Huh?
Where?
Find her now!
Hey, let's go this way.
Jeki!
Little girl!
Fuck!
Damn it!
Jeki!
Where the fuck are you, Missy?
Little girl!
Hey!
Fuck!
What the fuck is that sound?
Whistling.
The whistle of your death.
You fucking bitch!
Who the fuck are you?
Answer me!
Kill you…
I know this is strange.
I only met Monji two days ago.
No need to explain, Missy.
My name is 13.
13?
Do you want to be called 13?
All right then…
Missy.
Jeki?
Jeki!
Mommy!
Wake up, Mom.
Wake up.
Missy!
Wake up!
Hey, don't touch Monji!
Missy!
Don't.
Instructor…
Umbra.
Don't!
Run, Missy! You can do it!
Jeki!
Jeki...
Damn!
Fuck!
Why?
Why are you doing all this?
I don't know.
Why?
I have trained you well.
Why does it have to be like this?
Tell me.
This is how the world works.
I just want this to end.
It won't ever
end.
Mom.
Mom, wake up.
Motherfucker!
Instructor!
Your name…
Nomi!
Wake up, Nomi!
Mom.
Wake up, Mom.
Nomi.
The daughter of my heart.
MIRASTI, DAUGHTER OF SOEDARWO
Monji.
Hello, 13.
14.
I never liked the number 14.
It's strange.
But if I kill you now,
I'll be the next 13.
Fits me, right?
That's for "them" to decide.
Personally, I never…
liked you.
So
Perhaps it's for the best,
to finish you off.
Agree?
Who are you?
Someone who's here to even things out.
Well, now we're even.
Hey, Kid.
A Shadow is ready to die.
Are you?
On a second thought…
I rather kill you both slowly.
13.
She's only the beginning.
They'll come for you.
- Who?
- All of them.
Shadows.
Bayangan.
Shi no kage.
Who are you?
Burai?
Master Burai?
Umbra.
Did you kill her?
Alone, you'll doomed to die.
I have decided…
you are now my responsibility.
What say you, 13?
Call me Nomi.